{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Wall Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40017/":{"taskOID":40017,"originalTaskOID":40017,"setID":341,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7114,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Length","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7115,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How high will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4304,"questionDisplayText":"Use of Wall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the concrete wall?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7116,"questionDisplayText":"Applications and Finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special applications or finishes you would like for this project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color additives","answerDisplayText":"Special color additives","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Textured finish","answerDisplayText":"Textured finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6160,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco coating","answerDisplayText":"Stucco coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10883,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10884,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7114,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Length","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7115,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How high will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4304,"questionDisplayText":"Use of Wall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the concrete wall?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7116,"questionDisplayText":"Applications and Finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special applications or finishes you would like for this project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color additives","answerDisplayText":"Special color additives","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Textured finish","answerDisplayText":"Textured finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6160,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco coating","answerDisplayText":"Stucco coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10883,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10884,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color additives","answerDisplayText":"Special color additives","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Textured finish","answerDisplayText":"Textured finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6160,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stucco coating","answerDisplayText":"Stucco coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brick or stone veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10883,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10884,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40017/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40017,"taskName":"Poured Concrete Wall - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Poured Concrete Wall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Wall Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":353,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Poured Concrete buildings pour mason","textMessagingName":"Inst Concrete Wall","rolloverLongDesc":"Vertical structures require more elaborate forms that masons who work mostly with flat work might not have.","rolloverShortDesc":"Install or replace vertical concrete structures.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Poured Concrete Wall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Concrete Wall \u0026 Block Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Finish Poured Concrete Wall","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Poured Concrete Wall Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Poured Concrete Wall - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Wall Project","urlName":"Poured-Concrete-Wall-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Wall \u0026 Block Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Poured,Concrete,buildings,pour,mason,slab,fence","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":341,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}